This is our most advanced VR glasses yet
with almost no latency.
Try them on.
and you truly feel like you're going inside the video game.
Whoa. Did you hear that. Beavis?
Oh. yeah. he said. "Feel like you're going inside."
Uh. no. dumbass.
He said those glasses make you feel like
you're going inside a video game.
Let's try them. Beavis.
I've always wanted to. like. go inside a video game
and eat some coins and kick Luigi in the nads.
Yeah. that would be cool.
Uh. let's see here.
These ones look pretty cool.
Just put these on here.
- Whoa.
- These graphics are amazing.
- Wow.
It looks like we're really in some kind
of a mall or something.
Yeah. looks just like real life.
but it's a little bit darker.
It's amazing.
Whoa. look. They even have a Hot Topic.
This game kicks ass.
It's really amazing. Yeah.
Let's go kick ass on some noobs. yeah.
Is he trying to teach singing or reading?
I don't know. but I don't wanna learn either one.
Yeah. really.
Yeah. this is kinda catchy.
Yeah. that is kinda catchy.
It's like a song about your mom.
No. you're off. Butt-Head.
Wait a minute.
Shut up. Butt-Head.
What's in that purple door back there?
It's got. like. a padlock on it.
That's where he keeps his wife's skeleton.
That's pretty dark. Butt-Head.
Uh. sorry. Beavis.
Just trying to have a little fun.
Damn it. is he teaching counting now?
He's not even doing it right.
Yeah. One. two. three. one?
Yeah. it goes one. two. three. four.
Beat your meat upon the floor.
- Beat your meat.
Five. six. seven. eight.
beat your meat with a roller skate.
Beat your meat. Beat your meat.
13. 14. 15. 16...
Beat your meat without resisting.
Beat your meat. Beat your meat.
17. 18. 19. 20.
Beat your meat. you still got plenty.
Beat your meat. Beat your meat.
Uh...
Wait. what's nine. ten. eleven. twelve?
It's "nine. ten. eleven. twelve.
"beat your meat until it swells.
Beat your meat. Beat your meat."
Now that's a good song.
You know who would sing that song really good?
Adele.
Yeah. she'd be great. you know?
Give it a woman's perspective. you know.
Beat your meat. Beat your meat.
Whoa. It really is realistic.
It sure is. Beavis.
Let's go. like. look at stuff up close.
Whoa. check it out. Beavis.
It looks just like a real guy.
And his butt looks just like a real butt.
Wow. This technology has really come a long ways.
you know what I'm saying?
Whoa. and you can even interact with it. wow.
Hey. back off. buddy. What's wrong with you?
They even programmed him to act mad
when you stick your face in his butt.
It's amazing. It's just like a real mall.
Ow.
It feels just like real pain.
How do they do it?
Whoa. This is cool.
We're in the water level. Beavis.
- Check it out.
- Yeah.
I don't know. Butt-Head.
The water doesn't feel that real.
Feels kinda fake. actually.
I guess you have to. like. pay extra for the pro model.
Butt-Head. what are we supposed to do in this game?
You dumbass. don't you know anything about video games?
We're supposed to. like. go find some weapons.
and then at the end of the level.
- we kill a boss.
- Oh. yeah. yeah.
I think we need to. like. talk to some NPCs.
Hi. would you like to try our blueberry mint tea?
No. Can you. like. give us a mission?
Yeah. because we just started this game.
and we need. like. a flamethrower or something.
- What?
- We need a mission. dumbass.
Is there. like. someone we can kill
and then you'll give us a sword or something?
Can you guys just go do this somewhere else?
You can't just come up to people trying to--
Is there. like. a button to press
so we can skip him talking?
You can just come up to people trying to do their job.
- and just start saying weird...
- Hey. come on. Skip. Skip!
- To get a reaction.
- It's not working. Butt-Head.
I don't wanna have to call security.
That's not what I'm about. you know. man?
Skip. Come on. skip.
This interaction sucks.
Let's go find a flamethrower
so we can come back and blow him up.
"I don't wanna have to call security.
That's not what I'm about."
So what do we do now. Butt-Head?
Uh. well. let's see.
We're on level two of this game now.
so we probably have some new powers.
Cool. Like what?
Uh...
I think we can go outside
and. like. carjack a car or something.
And go get a laser gun or. like. a battle axe. Yeah.
Hmm. Let's see.
Which car should we jack?
That one looks pretty good.
Well. let's go carjack it.
Yeah. this is gonna be cool.
Hey. hey. slow down.
Hey. come back here.
Damn it. You screwed it all up. Beavis.
Damn it.
This game is hard.
I wanna start over.
Uh. yeah. good idea.
How do we do that?
We need to. like. die.
And then we can come back to life
at the beginning of the level and start over.
Oh. yeah. cool.
So how do we. like. die?
Uh...
I got an idea. Beavis.
Yeah? What is it?
Ah!
Uh...
You butthole. you're still alive.
Are you sure?
Damn it. Beavis. you suck at video games.
Let me show you how it's done.
Okay. here we go.
Just go ahead and--
Ooh! Uh!
Oh. my God. Are you okay?
Uh. no.
I'm still alive.
Get back in your car and run me over again. dumbass.
What are you doing?
One more oughta do it.
She dresses like what stupid people
think smart people dress like.
Uh. that that stuff. like.
at a crime scene?
Like. if you have DNA. it means you're guilty.
Oh. yeah. yeah.
That's why I never spank my monkey near a crime scene.
You know?
Oh. yeah.
That's pretty smart. Beavis.
Oh. God.
Firemen.
Yeah.
Those firemen. they're always. like.
like. being heroes.
And getting medals and stuff.
But all they do is just sit around and wait
and play checkers.
and. like. do bachelorette parties.
And then as soon as I wanna burn something.
they come and put it out.
I remember the first time I found out what firemen do.
I was little. and I was in this vacant lot.
and I started a fire.
and then the firemen showed up.
and then they brought out this firehose.
and I was like. yeah. cool. a firehose. yeah.
But guess what comes out of the firehose?
Just guess. I want you to guess.
Everyone knows what comes out of a firehose.
No. no. it's not what you think.
I'll give you a hint. It's not fire.
It's water! You believe that?
And then they just put it out.
and then they told me a bunch of stuff of how fire is bad.
and then they took me back to my mom.
You know. they should call them watermen. Yeah.
That's what I call them.
when I'm not calling them son of a bitches.
You thought firemen start fires?
Yeah. I mean.
you know. the garbageman just. like.
spreads garbage everywhere.
I mean. why not?
I just thought. you know. the firemen.
I mean. they did save my life four times. you know. so...
Yeah. maybe they're not all bad. I don't know.
Son of a bitches.
Never meet your heroes.
Whoa.
Whoa. I think it worked. Butt-Head.
We died. and we're at the beginning of the level.
These glasses are amazing.
Uh. Beavis?
What?
We're not wearing the glasses.
Oh. So we're not in the game anymore?
Uh. I guess not.
Oh. so we're just. like. in a hospital?
Uh. looks like it.
Damn it. This sucks.
Uh. wait a minute.
There's the glasses.
Whoa. It did work.
We're at the beginning of the level.
We're in some sort of hospital-like room.
Look. I've got a weapon.
- It's like a white club.
- Whoa.
I've got one too.
It's. like. a spear
with a bag on it.
Okay. Beavis.
Time to quit screwing around and go kill everything we see.
Oh. there you are.
Thank God you're alive.
- I'm so sorry--
- Let's kill him. Beavis.
What? Look. I don't blame you--
- Die!
- Club his ass. Beavis.
Ah! I understand why you're angry.
Ah!
Finally killing a boss. yeah!
I'll let you hit me two more times. but that's it.
Let's go kill the doctors.
Yeah! Yeah!